©
© P @ rM ! nder
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ ™
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ ™ Mobile - + 919815899536
They have this All Bird TV . You seen it ?
No . - Sure , it 's All Bird TV .
I 'm giving them a plug .
It 's all birds .
I watch it with the cat , the cat , fixated by it .
Damn it !
Damn it .
I am a goddamn genius .
Oh , my God .
Sebastian , do you have any idea what time it is ?
Da Vinci never slept .
Said it was a waste of time .
Who 's that ?
Not your business .
Not anymore .
Linda
I cracked the reversion .
You cracked it ?
Look at this .
Watch .
Eleven months and you suddenly come up with it out of the blue ? How ?
The usual . Coffee and Twinkies .
I hate you .
Can you find Matt and get to the lab ?
I want Isabelle for a live test .
I think I can find him .
When will you be in ?
Well , it should be daylight in Sweden now .
So I should call the Nobel committee and tell them to get our prize ready .
I 'll see you in a few .
Matt .
Sebastian called .
We gotta get to the lab .
What 's the rush ?
He cracked reversion .
You 're kidding .
When ? - While we were sleeping .
You want a ride ?
Maybe we should take our own cars .
I 'm tired of this sneaking around , Lin .
You 're gonna have to tell him eventually .
I will , eventually .
I 'm just waiting for the right time .
With Sebastian , there 's never gonna be a right time .
Morning , Dr. Caine . - Morning .
Have a nice day , sir . - Thank you .
Good morning , sir . - Morning , Ed .
Your team 's in early today .
Something special ?
Sorry , Ed . You know the rules .
Authorization , please . - Caine , 0027 .
Confirmed .
Hi .
Isabelle .
Come on , Isabelle .
Calm down , baby .
Good girl .
It 's okay .
I 'm not gonna hurt you .
Hold still .
Isabelle ?
She 's more aggressive these days .
That 's what tranquillizers are for .
I 'll get her .
She 's been gone too long .
It 's starting to affect her brain .
You take care of that bite . - I 'll manage .
Hey .
Ten bucks says I nail her first .
You 're on .
Isabelle ?
Got a surprise for you .
You missed .
Maybe because I don 't spend my lunch hours practicing .
You owe me ten .
Put it on my tab .
You know , someday I may actually make you pay up .
Sarah 's on the warpath , so you play nice .
This is bullshit , Sebastian .
- And good morning to you too .
Get the monkey on the table .
How can you justify injecting Isabelle with the serum without even testing it ?
Because it 'll save time .
Then you can mop up afterwards .
You think I 'm trying to kill Isabelle ?
Kill ? More like liquefy .
- Lab 's prepped .
Well , your objections are duly noted and summarily overruled .
Yes , sir .
How come when you say , ' Yes ,
sir , ' it sounds like ' Fuck you ' ?
Practice .
How 'd you convince me to hire her ?
You wanted the best vet in the U.S.
She cares more about the animals .
- And maybe that 's why she 's so good .
So this guy you 're seeing , what 's he like ?
He 's everything you 're not .
He must be dull .
Ready in 40 . - Okay .
Vitals ?
All normal .
Using the word ' normal ' loosely , of course .
Emergency medical , standing by . - Tech , status ?
This is God .
You are disturbing the natural order of things
and will be severely punished for all eternity .
God has spoken .
How many times must I tell you , Frank
you 're not God .
I am .
Sorry , chief . Forgot .
You guys ready to roll yet ?
Yes .
Like those sorry-ass M.D. S have ever had to wait for us .
Tell His Highness Mary was hot two hours ago .
Yeah , I 'll tell him that .
Ready up here , chief .
- Roll and record .
Rolling .
Subject , Isabelle Two .
Currently in phase-shift , 126 hours .
Testing D-phase protocol
Serial Irradiated Protein Caine 125 .
Stop naming them after yourself , you 'd have better luck .
Thank you , Dr. Kensington , for that keen observation .
I 'll include it in my memoirs .
I 'll make sure to put you in mine .
Would you guys be serious , please ?
You think she 'll make it ?
- I don 't know , I just work here .
Quantum signatures are calibrated .
Okay , Sarah , get us a vein .
Spray .
Vein 's prepped .
All right .
Here goes nothing .
Bad form , Matthew .
The honor is mine .
Okay .
Injection occurred at 0847 .
Elevated heartbeat .
We 're still in the green . - Confirmed .
Bioelectric energy and quantum shift indicators are stable .
We 're getting cellular reaction .
It 's working . It 's actually working .
Of course it is .
- Don 't get cocky .
Heart rate 's up . She 's scared . It 's okay .
Subject began manifesting immediately .
Protocol 's acting quickly .
Goddamn it , blood pressure crashing . Pulse high .
It 's her heart .
I got erratic heartbeat and brain activity .
She 's going into cardiac arrest . - Defib !
Prep an intracardiac .
Flatline . We 're losing her .
- No , we 're not . Hit her !
Clear !
Again . - Clear .
Again ! - Clear .
Come on . - Again !
Clear !
Fuck ! Intracardiac .
Wait ! No , we got something .
Still erratic
and stabilizing .
Oh , man .
Brain activity returning to normal .
Quantum signatures are stable .
Welcome back , Isabelle .
Yeah . Yeah !
Yeah , baby !
We did it . - Good work , everyone .
Yeah ! That 's the way it 's done , man .
So how 's she doing , doc ?
Well , I think she 's gonna be okay .
Come on . Right in there .
- Come on , Isabelle .
Go ahead . Good girl .
Look how peaceful she is .
It seems like nothing happened to her .
Schedule a vivisection for Monday .
I wanna check her neuropathways .
You just brought her back and you 're gonna slice up her brain ?
I 'm not running a goddamn zoo !
You 're a fucking unethical bastard .
- Tell her you 're kidding .
Right ? - Right .
I won 't cut her for another week .
Don 't be such an asshole .
We finally have something to celebrate .
Cool . I 'm hungry , let 's go . - Me too .
We should cut you up .
Ladies and gentlemen , a moment of your time , please .
Here it comes .
To the finest research team I have ever known .
Cheers .
There was a big explosion , and afterward she said :
'lf you 're so smart , how come you 're still in the second grade ? '
She grew her eyebrows back ? - In a month .
How long were you suspended ? - A month .
Hey , I thought you 'd gone .
There 's nowhere to go .
Did I miss something ?
Aren 't you supposed to be happy ?
Reversion was the last breakthrough .
Feels like the beginning of the end .
That 's not true .
We 've got a lifetime of data .
Matt has the patience to crunch the numbers , but you know me
I need this grandeur and the spectacle .
I can 't concern myself with the details .
Yeah , I know .
I was one of them .
I thought we were great together .
You were great .
I was just standing next to you .
Come on .
We had some good times .
Yeah , we had some good times .
Have you ever wanted to turn the clock back ?
Go back and try again ?
I 'd say that kind of time travel doesn 't exist .
Well , maybe we should invent it .
Or not .
What 's it like ?
Four years ago , this committee gave me
a very specific and challenging task
to phase-shift a human being out of quantum sync
with the visible universe
and return him safely with no aftereffects .
We found that sending them to never-never land was easy .
It 's the getting them back that 's hard .
Primary DNA strands decaying on you ?
Along with cellular bond instability .
How have you solved the problem ?
I haven 't .
But we 're close .
We just need more time .
Ever since you walked in my class your freshman year
I knew you were different .
Over the years , your genius has been most impressive .
Thank you , Dr. Kramer .
Well , don 't thank me yet .
This committee has given you remarkable leeway .
We 've tolerated your eccentricities , as well as your need for privacy .
And I assure you , our patience is running out .
If we don 't get results and get them soon
your genius will cease to impress me .
And if you can 't make it work
I 'll find another Sebastian Caine who can .
What just happened in there ?
- This better be good .
I wasn 't ready for them to know .
- You weren 't ready ?
Being ready 's not it .
You have results , you report them .
Can I explain ?
- You just lied to the Pentagon !
Once they know we 've completed it
what 's to stop them from taking over the project ?
Why would they ?
- Because they won 't need us .
But it 's their project .
It 's gonna happen sometime .
It may be their project , but it 's my dream , my vision .
What are you proposing ?
- That we go to Phase Three ourselves .
Phase Three ? Are you nuts ?
You can 't jump into human testing .
There 's rules , procedures .
You don 't make history with rules .
You make it by seizing the moment .
You wanna be the first one .
That 's what this is about .
This is not about me , it 's about us .
We said we would change the world .
Now is our chance .
And we 'll get the Nobel Prize .
Come on , buddy .
You know , if somebody finds out that we bypassed advisory review
we 're never gonna work again .
- But if it works , no one 'll care .
How did you get clearance for Phase Three ?
I volunteered . They approved . - No way .
You 're kidding .
You volunteered ?
Are you insane ?
Jonas Salk tested the polio vaccine on himself .
Was he insane ?
Yeah , I 'm pretty sure he was .
Shit .
In the past four weeks , we have brought back seven primates .
The results speak for themselves .
- Or do you wanna believe that ?
Sarah , I thought you 'd be happy .
We are giving the animals a break .
Moving this fast is bad science , no matter who the guinea pig is .
I can 't believe they approved this .
- I think it 's fucking cool .
You would .
If we 're to move forward , this is the next logical step .
I 'll stay shifted for three days and then we 'll perform a quantum reversion .
Fuck , yes .
Can I count on your best work ?
Good .
How did we let him talk us into this ?
Can we talk about it later ?
I 'm trying to make love to you .
We 're risking our professional lives here .
Yes , Matt , I realize .
Then why did we agree to it ?
Because we 're suckers .
And because sometimes when you get to the edge of the map
you have to keep sailing to see what 's out there .
And maybe because we both know that Sebastian can pull it off .
Let me ask another question .
- Is it about who 's gonna be on top ?
Ever miss being with him ?
Why do you ask that ?
- Because he sets the bar pretty high .
Let me tell you a little secret .
The concept of Sebastian is much more appealing
than Sebastian himself .
Whereas you ...
You 're methodical
precise
and very , very thorough .
And besides
you fit better .
We 're ready for you .
See you later .
It 's not too late to stop .
- I thought I was the nervous one .
We have a lot riding on this .
Hear about Superman and Wonder Woman ?
Stop clowning around .
- It 's a good one .
Superman is flying over Metropolis .
He 's horny and checking out the rooftops .
He sees Wonder Woman sunning on the roof of the Justice League .
She 's lying there buck-naked , spread - eagle , wanting to be fucked , right ?
Superman says to himself :
'I gotta get myself some Wonder pussy . '
Then he realizes that he could fly down , do a little fast pumping
and be gone before she knew , since he 's Superman .
Faster than a speeding bullet .
He swoops down , he fucks her so quick , she doesn 't even see him .
Wonder Woman sits up , says , ' What the fuck was that ? '
And the Invisible Man says , ' I don 't know
but my asshole is killing me . '
That 's funny , right ?
Come on , guys .
That 's funny .
Ladies , please .
This is science .
Starting IV drip .
Okay , how are you feeling ?
- I 'm a little tense .
Pulse 88 . BP 140 / 95 .
It 's a bit elevated .
I wonder why .
Are you sure ?
Positive .
We ready up in heaven ? - Ready .
Mary 's rolling .
I just hope we 're not making a snuff film . Rolling .
If it is , I got dibs on his Porsche .
Janice , how can you say that ?
Sorry .
Porsche is mine .
Subject male , age 38 , weight 166 pounds .
Serum 's irradiated .
This better work . - It will .
Oh , yeah ? - You wanna bet on it ?
If I win , you won 't be around to pay off , so , no .
Are you ready ?
I 'll do it .
So if anything goes wrong , you can 't be blamed .
All right .
Any last words ?
Yeah . If I die , pretend I said something deep and clever .
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ ™
©
© P @ rM ! nder
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ
©
© P @ rM ! nder
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ
Injection administered at 1823 .
Are you feeling anything ?
- Nothing so far .
Vitals are stable .
- Nothing 's happening .
Human DNA structure may take more time .
You pulsed it right ? - Yes .
Recheck the radiation .
It can 't be non-reactive .
No change in bioelectric activity .
Goddamn it !
I 'll repeat the protocol , okay ? - Wait .
I 'm starting to feel something .
It 's my arm . It 's ...
It 's getting warm .
Okay , it 's starting to tingle .
Yeah , it 's moving down into my back .
Here we go .
Shit ! It hurts .
It 's tearing me .
Heartbeat 's elevated .
Pulse at 110 . 130 .
Christ , didn 't think it would hurt so much .
Frank , readouts !
Brain waves are spiking .
He 's on the verge of a seizure .
Pulse is 165 , 170 .
Blood pressure 180 over 110 .
Sebastian , can you hear me ?
Sebastian ?
His heart 'll blow out !
- Standby paddles !
Coming in .
Subcellular quantum .
He 's shifting .
Bioelectric in the red .
Wait .
He 's going .
Pulse is 180 .
Holding stable .
Holy shit .
Pulse is dropping . 170 , 160 , 150 .
Bio-quantum phase-shift occurred at 1826 .
Is he okay ?
Yeah , he 's in bioelectric shock .
Passed out from the trauma .
Vitals returning to normal ?
Pulse 110 , dropping .
Blood pressure 's 130l75 .
Quantum readings normal .
- Electrical activity is stabilizing .
Something to tell the grandkids .
Pulse steady at 85 .
You did it .
You 're the first .
It 's okay . It 's okay .
You nodded off .
His breathing 's hypnotic . - Yeah .
How long has it been ?
Seventeen hours .
And we already have enough data for two lifetimes of research .
It 's a brave new world , Lin .
I keep looking at that hole , wondering if he 's really there .
Did you see that ?
- Sebastian , can you hear me ?
Christ ! The lights !
Turn off the goddamn lights !
I can 't close my eyes .
You can , but your eyelids are transparent .
It 's weird .
I feel the same , but I 'm not here .
You 're here .
Sebastian ? - I 'm right here .
Where ? - At the mirror .
Looking at myself .
Or , rather , not looking at myself .
Hey , how 's he doing ?
Why don 't you ask Sebastian ?
How do you feel ?
- Oh , not too bad , considering .
Just wanna set the mood .
It 's the light .
His eyelids are transparent .
So , what 's it like being a ghost ?
Ghosts are dead .
I 'm very much alive .
Come on , don 't be a dick .
Sorry . I couldn 't resist .
Okay , now I feel like we 're playing Marco Polo .
I wonder where he is now .
Well , I see the procedure 's not changed your personality .
He just brushed by me .
- No worries , I 'm on it .
Do you see anything ?
- Where is he ?
You got him ?
Sebastian ?
Got you , chief .
You guys have no sense of fun .
Shit . Oh , my God .
I 've arranged for one of us to be here 24l7 , if you need anything .
The team 's gonna be on alpha-call alert , so we can be here within ...
Thirty minutes . I know .
I wrote the procedure , remember ?
I was reassuring you .
There 's a thermal camera for observation .
She likes this , doesn 't she ? - What ?
Being in charge .
- Oh , yeah . She loves it .
It 's about time the shoe was on the other foot .
Well , just remember .
It 's still my project .
You okay taking the late shift ?
- It 's not like I have a social life .
I know . The workaholic 's curse .
Carter 's gonna be in by 6 to spell you .
I 'm here at 8 .
Call me if you need to .
I 'll be fine . Get some sleep .
Okay . Bye . - Bye .
Sarah ?
Are you awake ?
Sebastian ?
Are you in here ?
I know you 're in here .
Then when I checked the monitor again , he 's back in the bed .
When I ask him where he 'd been , he said he 's getting coffee .
Why didn 't you call me ?
- Because I wasn 't sure .
I 'm still not .
I mean , I could have been dreaming .
I just thought I should tell someone .
What do you wanna do ?
I don 't know .
I have a tough time believing he 'd be that crude .
I feel so stupid .
Why don 't I talk to him ?
I 'll see what he says ...
No , don 't .
You know , it 's probably nothing .
I shouldn 't have mentioned it .
So how was your first night ? - Restless .
Hard to sleep without closing your eyes .
What 'd you do ?
Got up a couple of times .
Walked around .
Sarah mentioned you weren 't in your room .
I got a cup of coffee .
In the future , you 'll wanna tell the on-call where you 're going
just in case something happens to you .
I 'm touched by your concern , but it 's not a problem .
We don 't want it to become one .
Everything 's normal .
All right , let 's get these off .
You okay ?
Yeah . Why ?
You seem a little nervous .
No , I 'm fine .
Are you looking at me ?
No .
Why ?
No reason .
What was the clientele like ?
- This guy comes up to me and says :
'I like my women like my coffee .
' People still use that line ?
Maybe he meant cold and bitter . - Very funny .
I gotta take a leak .
Keep Carter away from my food .
I 'll try , but I can 't promise .
- All right .
It 'd be freaky , but it 'd settle down .
No , what would you do if you knew you couldn 't be seen ?
It gives me the creeps .
I can 't take a piss without wearing my thermals .
Like anyone wants to see that .
- How do I know ?
Are you asking what we 'd do or what Sebastian would do ?
The difference ?
There 's human nature , then there 's Sebastian .
He 's always joking that he 's God .
Imagine what he 'd do if left to his own devices .
Scary thought .
Thankfully , it 's almost over . - Hallelujah .
It 's just beginning .
You think Sebastian 's bad ?
Lmagine if the military gets their hands on this .
Better our military than someone else 's .
Sebastian , goddamn it .
You have no idea how much fun this is .
You should try it .
I 'm sure I 'll have my chance .
Hey , relax .
It 's my last night , so I thought we 'd try one more experiment .
Sebastian .
Can you guess what this is ?
What ?
How did it feel ?
A little too familiar .
Wanna know what it 's like to make love to an invisible man ?
It 'd just be like old times .
- What do you mean ?
You were never there .
Well , I 'm here now .
We talked about this once , remember ?
What ?
You wondered if you 'd know the difference .
Sebastian , I do know the difference .
It 's not what I don 't see .
It 's what I don 't feel .
Get some rest .
Got a big day tomorrow .
Subject : Dr. Sebastian Caine .
Currently in phase-shift 86 hours , 23 minutes .
D - phase protocol . Injecting Serial Protein Caine 127 .
Irradiation complete .
Set .
Are you ready ?
- Not really .
I was starting to enjoy myself .
Well , tough .
We 'll see you in a minute , my friend .
Injection occurred at 0928 .
What are you feeling ?
Something 's not right .
Heartbeat elevated . Frank .
Shift indicators are erratic .
Bioelectric 's jumping .
- Check radiation . Crash cart .
What ?
What 's happening ?
I can 't breathe .
Check his airway .
- His lungs are seized . Intubate .
Carter !
Tube him !
Sebastian .
He 's going into phase-shift .
- Get him on the table .
We lost our signals .
Goddamn !
Get me an IV of AG-7 .
- I 'm on it .
No pulse .
I 've got no pulse !
Starting CPR .
Don 't you die on me .
Don 't you fucking die on me .
- I 'm getting a pulse .
Sebastian , can you hear me ?
- He 's going into shock .
Jesus .
Hi .
So I guess it didn 't work .
No .
You look worried .
Must 've been bad .
You almost died .
Whatever doesn 't kill me makes me stronger .
Yeah , and ends our careers .
What are we gonna tell Kramer ?
Nothing .
He doesn 't need to know yet .
We can 't keep lying to the others .
- We don 't have a choice .
If I 'm gonna be stuck like this for a while
we 'll have to make a few adjustments .
Done .
Open . - Here .
Okay , lift .
Carter , get the fan .
Okay , don 't move .
Don 't move .
Thanks . That 's better .
Here you go .
It 's an improvement .
- You 'd almost pass for human .
He couldn 't before .
- You have a face you can talk to now .
We can all work in normal light again .
Let 's see if we can 't try to figure out what went wrong .
Before he starts biting people too .
Goddamn it ! - What ?
I lost cohesion again .
Are you any closer ? - No .
You know , I can 't figure out the B and C of it .
The B and C ?
My 5th grade teacher told me that genius is getting from A to D
without having to go through B and C.
Sebastian can do that .
But me , I gotta have the B and C.
Hold on , Sebastian .
We 're almost there .
Come on , guys .
Out of the way !
I can 't take much more testing .
I know how hard it is .
Bullshit . You don 't know anything .
This isn 't easy for any of us .
Fuck you , Matt ! It is easy for you .
I was to be in phase-shift for three days .
It 's been 10 fucking days , all right ? !
Ten days of tissue tests , radiation tests and your fucking needles !
I can 't fucking take it anymore .
What I meant was ... - Fuck what you meant !
And don 't ever ...
Don 't ever tell me how hard you have it .
Come on , Sebastian , you 're tired and you need to rest .
I can 't believe I gotta spend another night in this place .
We 're trying to do everything we can .
Yeah , that 's not enough .
There she is .
I 'd suck the tits right off of you .
Hey .
Dr. Caine , what 's going on ?
wonk uoy tel ot yb deppots tsuJ . elihw a rof tuo gniog m 'I
Wait . Going out ?
Hold it a second . Dr. Caine .
Sebastian .
Dr. Caine .
What do you mean ?
If I don 't get out , I 'll go nuts .
You can 't leave the compound . - Why not ?
It 's the rule .
- It 's my rule , I just changed it .
Authorization .
- Caine 0027 .
Confirmed .
- You can 't just change it .
I 'm not gonna spend my life in this godforsaken dump !
I 'm going out ! Be back in a couple of hours !
Oh , shit !
Hello ? - It 's Carter . We got a problem .
How 's it going , Ed ? - Hey , doc .
I haven 't seen you in a while .
- You know how it is sometimes .
Work , work , work .
I was beginning to worry because your car hadn 't moved .
Thanks a lot , Ed .
But everything 's cool .
Hey , look . Look .
Look at that .
- Man , he 's weird .
Oh , my God . - Mommy ! Mommy !
Mommy ! Mommy ! - What ?
What ? - Look , it 's a ghost .
Don 't be ridiculous .
- Mom , it 's a ghost .
I 'll meet you at the lab .
I 'll go by his place just in case .
I 'll see you there .
He could be here .
He could be anywhere .
Shit .
Don 't even think about it .
Who 's gonna know ?
Sebastian ?
Oh , shit .
Matt , it 's me .
He was here .
No , he took his mask off .
He must be outside somewhere .
I don 't know where he went .
I 'm coming back to the lab .
How ? How am I supposed to do that ?
I can 't fucking see him .
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ ™
©
© P @ rM ! nder
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ ™
©
© P @ rM ! nder
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ
You say you want us to shoot him ? I 'm in .
It 's not a monkey , it 's Dr. Caine .
Aren 't we overreacting here ?
I don 't give a rat 's ass if we are .
Out there , he 's at risk .
If someone finds out what he is , the whole program is destroyed .
Jeez , relax .
Nobody 's gonna find out .
Can I still shoot him ?
- Where have you been ?
I told Carter .
I was getting stir-crazy .
I went home to pick up stuff .
Bullshit .
I went to your apartment .
You did more than ' pick up stuff . '
What are you talking about ?
- You , of all people . How could you ?
What did you see in my apartment ?
I saw your face , your clothes .
Sebastian , in public .
Why 'd you have to go out in public ?
I 'm still project leader .
It 's my decision to make .
You 're right . It 's your decision .
But if you leave again , I swear I 'll go straight to the committee .
Throw your career away ?
Not likely .
Try me .
So that 's it , huh ?
I 'm officially a fucking lab rat .
You volunteered .
You knew the consequences .
Next time you do inventory , get me an exercise wheel .
Yeah , sure .
Let 's pack it up and go home .
Exercise wheel ?
Was he serious ?
- What do you think ?
Hey , Lin . - Yeah ?
The committee knows what we 've done , don 't they ?
Shit , Lin ! - Won 't matter if we can get him back .
I can 't believe you did that !
- You have deniability , you didn 't know .
All I ask is please , please don 't fuck us .
Think she 'll say anything ?
- No , she 's in too far .
She doesn 't worry me . - Sebastian .
He 's been gone longer than the animals .
It might affect his mind .
What if it already has ?
Hold still .
Good .
So , what was it like ?
- What do you mean ?
When you were out in the world .
- I just walked around . You know .
You just walked around .
Come on , there 's more , right ?
Like what ?
Man , if it was me
I 'd be fucking with people , whispering in ears .
I 'd be hanging out at Victoria 's Secret .
I 'd be the king .
Childish , don 't you think ?
No .
Well , it was late .
I wasn 't out for very long .
Did you see anybody ?
There was this one girl .
Did you mess with her ? - No .
Well , maybe I scared her a little . - Yeah ?
How 'd that feel ?
I liked it .
Nice .
Hello . - Lin .
Remember the B and C ?
I think I found it .
55 percent reversion .
That 's the best we 've gotten yet .
Protein structure was a dead end .
Key was to manipulate radiation signature .
75 percent . 80 percent .
82 . - Come on .
We 've got it .
No , it 's slowing .
Be an optimist .
- It 's slowing down .
88 . 92 percent .
93 percent .
94 percent .
95 percent .
No ! - Shit !
Cellular bonds are collapsing .
- Full quantum cascade at 95 percent .
Some breakthrough .
If I were on a table right now ,
I 'd be a steaming pile of flesh .
Don 't tempt me .
We 're closer , which counts .
Closer ! He just traded quantum energy for stability !
It 's ludicrous . - Come on .
You 're pissed you didn 't think of it . - Really ?
95 percent ?
That 's not even worth my time !
For Christ sake .
Asshole .
At least now we have some hope .
What ?
You 're a fucking moron .
What is your problem ?
Matt is onto something and he could use your help .
Matt . Oh , yeah .
Yeah , he 's onto something , all right .
He 's on my coattails .
He 's been riding them for years .
Get off your fucking pedestal .
He 's trying like hell to fix you .
Or kill me .
And you know what the sad part is ?
I have this gift and I can 't even use it .
So now it 's a gift .
Damn right it 's a gift .
If you weren 't so shortsighted ,
you 'd let me out of this cage to explore it .
If you weren 't so shortsighted , you 'd be with us trying to save your life .
My life ?
I have no fucking life .
I 'm a prisoner .
No , you 're not a prisoner . - Oh , yeah ?
Is that what you think when you leave here at night ?
Is that how you alleviate your guilt
when I 'm stuck in this shithole and you 're at home
fucking your boyfriend ?
What bothers you most ?
That you don 't have a life
or that I do ?
Frank , I 'm coming down to the lab .
Don 't you sleep ?
Da Vinci never slept .
- Okay . I 'm here if you need me .
No , no , no , no .
Hello .
Motherfucker ...
If you were any later , I would have started without you .
Jesus !
I don 't see anything .
Hello ?
No .
No , he 's here .
Yes , I 'm sure .
I 'm staring at him .
Is something wrong ?
You want me to wake him ?
- No , I was just checking .
Who the fuck does she think she is ?
I 'm not good enough for her ?
I 'm not good enough ?
I 'll show them both how good I am .
Quiet !
You wanna fuck with me , bitch ?
You know what happens when you fuck with me ? !
Don 't worry .
Nobody 's gonna hurt you . No one .
My , you 're looking spry this morning . - Oh , yeah .
There 's nothing more stimulating than staying up
watching someone else sleep .
Good morning , gang .
Good morning .
Hi , Maggie . Good morning , girls .
Sebastian
you awake ?
I am now .
Notice anything unusual last night ?
Nope , nothing at all . Why ?
Franklin 3 , he 's dead .
So ?
So I thought maybe you heard something .
I was asleep .
- Yeah , all night ?
Are you accusing me of something ?
No , it just doesn 't make sense , does it , a dog dying just like that ?
Look , I know how you feel about them ,
Sarah , but animals do die .
It 's simply a fact of life .
That 's all night .
So he never left the room ?
- Yeah , I guess .
I don 't know .
Why would he kill a dog , right ?
Hello ?
Sebastian ?
Sebastian , this is not funny .
What are you doing here ? - Where is he ?
He 's asleep , why ?
I 'll be right back .
Sebastian ?
Matt , activate alpha call .
I want everyone in here now .
Working late ?
- That 's what they pay us for .
It 's really pretty clever .
All it does is loop the same image .
What do we do now ? Go after him ?
No . We 're going to the committee .
Shouldn 't we wait and talk to him ?
He killed a dog with his bare hands .
You were there ?
- He went out every night
with absolute disregard for his safety and ours .
What 's he done ?
- I don 't wanna think about it .
Are we in trouble ?
- You didn 't mislead the committee .
We 'll take responsibility .
What do we do when he comes back ? - Nothing .
The committee will bring security .
We 'll brief you tomorrow morning .
Authorization , please .
- McKay 1-Delta-835 .
You sure about this ?
- It 's the right thing to do .
Given Sebastian 's history , this behavior doesn 't surprise me .
You should 've said something .
I had a lot of faith in you , thinking you 'd take care of this .
I know what we did was wrong .
Wrong doesn 't even begin to describe it .
Let 's leave it here .
I 'll call General Caster and convene the committee .
You go back to the lab .
We 'll handle him .
Is there anything we can do ?
You might think about clearing out your offices .
For what it 's worth , we 're both very sorry .
A little late for apologies .
Howard ?
What was that about ?
Just a screwup at work . - How bad ?
Bad enough to wake a few generals .
Hi , boss .
Martha !
Help !
Howard ? - Help ! Help !
Howard !
Why so jumpy ?
- You just surprised me .
No ' good morning ' for me today ?
You don 't love me anymore .
Just in a hurry . - Well , that 's okay .
It 's gonna be a busy day .
When did he get back ?
Three a. m . He 's been wandering around the lab ever since .
Kramer called yet ?
He 's probably still meeting with the committee .
We should have heard something .
I 'm calling .
Hello , is Dr. Kramer there ?
What ?
Oh , my God .
What 's wrong ?
- He 's dead .
What ? - He drowned in his pool last night .
General Caster , please .
Hello . Hello ?
There 's no dial tone .
There 's no outside line here either .
- We 'd better alert security .
Authorization , please .
- McKay 1-Delta-835 .
Authorization invalid .
Request denied .
That 's a first . McKay 1-Delta-835 .
Authorization invalid . Request denied .
Let me try mine .
Kensington 2-Romeo-159 .
Authorization invalid .
Request denied .
We 've got a problem .
I don 't believe this .
When will they start looking for us ?
- It could take a couple of days .
Can you hack into the system ?
- Already in .
Some security system .
- It 's just he 's extraordinary .
Someone 's more extraordinary than me .
What is it ? - The system 's fine .
Our access codes have been removed .
There 's only one left .
So we 're trapped ?
- We 'll get him .
Let me have one .
Sebastian ?
He 's not in here .
Okay , Sebastian , fun 's over .
Tell us where you are .
Sorry , Linda , but I can 't let you turn me in .
Sebastian , where are you ?
You have no idea what it 's like .
The power of it , the freedom .
I can 't let that go .
Whatever you 're planning , the phones , the elevator
it 's not gonna work .
They know about you .
No , they don 't .
Kramer died before he could tell a soul .
I saw to that .
Jesus .
You realize what you 're saying ?
- It 's amazing what you can do
when you don 't have to look at yourself in the mirror anymore .
Sebastian . - Goodbye , Linda .
Sebastian !
Shit !
Where 's Janice ?
She was right behind us .
Oh , fuck .
Oh , fuck . Oh , my God !
Janice ? Janice !
Janice ?
In there .
Darts . - Is it Sebastian ?
Oh , my God .
Shit !
She was right behind us .
How could he do this ?
He snapped . He fucking snapped .
It 's worse .
He 's thought this through . - What ?
He knew we were gonna turn him in .
He knew that his career would be over and his only way out
is to make sure no one knows what he is or what he 's done .
Which means he 'll get rid of us .
- Goddamn you !
You could 've stopped this ! - Back off .
You risked our lives ! - Shut up !
Don 't tell her to shut up ! She 's right !
I don 't care if she 's right !
I don 't care whose fault this is !
I just wanna know , what do we do now ?
Frank , can you restore the codes ?
I 'll try . - We can 't afford to sit here and wait .
We are not gonna wait .
We are gonna take him down .
Ever use this thing before ?
We designed it to help find the rats we kept dropping .
Too small for thermal scans .
Connecting . - Powering up .
Activating motion detectors .
We 've got movement .
Corridor six . - There he is .
Got it .
Check . - Check .
Matt , be careful .
- Just watch our backs .
Ready ? - Let 's do it .
Take a left at the next corridor .
Could we trap him in corridor eight ?
If he keeps heading that way .
- I 'm on five .
Anything ? - I think we can climb out .
There 's a ladder in the elevator shaft .
Shit , I lost him .
I lost him .
- He stopped moving .
It 's me . It 's me .
You have anything ? - No , nothing .
How did he get by us ?
He couldn 't have .
Sebastian !
There . Behind the pipes .
Dr. Caine ?
Can you hear me ?
- I 'm taking him down .
Cover me .
Covered .
It 's just a vent .
It 's just a goddamn vent .
Let him go ! Let him fucking go !
Matt , what 's happening ?
Carter 's down ! He 's hurt bad !
Get out of there .
Where the fuck is Sebastian ? !
Shit . He 's right on top of you !
Where 's he headed ? !
- He 's coming this way , to the lab .
The doors are closing !
He 's shutting me in !
You have him ? - I do .
He 's still there .
He 's on your side of the door .
Where ? - He 's right in front of you .
He 's coming at you !
I got thermals all over the place .
Five or six .
I 'm losing resolution !
He 's pumping out heat .
You won 't be able to see him .
The air 's the same temperature as his body .
He 's trapped . - I 'm going .
It 's not safe .
- Get Carter ! Meet at the lab .
We shouldn 't separate ! - Get Carter .
Marco . Polo .
You missed .
Now 'd be a good time to pay that tab .
- Come on ! You think you can take me ? !
Come on !
What happened to you ?
Was it the serum that fucked you up , or the power ?
Aren 't you the fucked up one ? !
Dining on my leftovers
no life except the one you borrowed from me !
Even with Linda .
- She left you , remember ?
Jesus Christ , I can 't imagine what the fuck she sees in a loser like you !
I 'm not a deranged asshole !
No , but you 're weak !
I thought killing you would be hard !
But I kind of like it .
Oh , my God . Fuck !
His pulse is weak !
His breathing 's shallow !
He 'll be okay ! - No , it 's severe !
He 's gonna be okay !
- Get down here !
Keep applying pressure until I get back !
Where you going ? - He needs blood .
Wait for the others !
- If I wait , he 'll die !
Sarah ! Fuck !
Sebastian ?
Sarah ?
God , I told them to meet us here .
Frank ?
Oh , God .
Come on . Give me one step , Sebastian .
One fucking step .
Move !
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ ™
©
© P @ rM ! nder
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ
Fuck .
Hey .
Quite a mess .
Fuck ! You motherfuck ...
Get off !
We had so much fun the last time .
- No , please don 't . Please .
Sweet dreams .
You know
I 've always admired your feistiness .
Goddamn it , Carter !
Don 't die on me now !
Sarah , I 'm losing him ! Sarah ! - Frank .
Where is she ? - He needed blood .
She went alone ?
- He would 've died !
He 's dead .
Come on .
Wait .
Sarah ?
Matt . - Keep spraying .
Oh , no .
Nothing .
What 's happening ? !
She 's dead , isn 't she ?
Motherfucker !
Frank !
Jesus .
I got it . I got it .
Oh , God !
Bye-bye , Linda .
Have fun with your boyfriend .
We 're locked in .
How bad ?
You 're losing blood , but he didn 't hit any organs .
Frank ? - No .
I gotta find something to close the wound .
Shit .
Talk to me .
Everything is spinning .
Are you still with me ?
- I can 't feel anything .
Can you feel this ?
A little .
Come on .
I need you to fight this .
I need you to stay awake . - I 'm trying .
Come on . Talk to me .
Talk to me !
Matt . Matt ! Matt !
Hello , face .
We are not gonna die in here .
I 'll be back with help . I promise .
Authorization , please .
- Caine 0027 .
Confirmed . - Thank you .
Sebastian !
I can 't let you leave .
- Sorry , you don 't have a choice .
Oh , yes , I do .
You think you 're God ?
I 'll show you God !
Shit !
I always knew you were a bitch !
Bitch !
No wonder it didn 't work out between us !
Stay the fuck away from her !
Thought I 'd save you for a change .
Come on . I heard an explosion !
Don 't touch it ! - What ?
It 's nitro .
- We gotta stop it .
No , we can 't ! Come on !
There 's a ladder in the elevator .
Can you climb ?
- Do I have a choice ?
You go first .
Move !
Oh , shit .
Stick to the side !
Let 's coming back down !
Down ! Go down !
Holy shit .
We better go before it slips .
Matt !
Get off of me ! Get off of me !
Matt .
Let go of me !
- One last kiss .
For old times ' sake .
Go to hell .
Come on .
Oh , my God .
Not God .
Not anymore .
© P @ rM ! nder M @ nkÖÖ ™